Hey dude. Sorry to send you this. I
had the best day that I've had in
at least half a year.
And I went over to help Don sell
his knee scooter. The one you bend
your knee and your leg is broken.
So I went over and did that like
Don wanted me to. And after that I
went to the supermarket.
And I walked around because I
couldn't figure out what I wanted.
So it took a little time.
And then I stopped at another store
and I got stuck there for a little
while walking around.
I come back here to your mom's
house and her car is open in the
garage and the car is not there.
I'm like that's weird. I'm thinking
she didn't have to go to a church
thing or something with her friends
or with the women at the church in
her rosary society. And then I'm
thinking maybe it's an emergency.
I don't know. So anyway, I come in
the house, see Scottie, pet
Scottie, come downstairs, just like
unpacking my stuff.
I'm like what? And then she
screamed, there are strangers at
Tree and Don's house.
And I drove over there because the
neighbors were calling Tree and
saying there's this weird guy
walking in and out of their house
and then doing something in the
garage. And it was me. Dude, I had
a flashback to when my dad punched
me in the face from going sledding
and I know you know that story.
The part is the enemy people said
do everything you can to stay away
from getting upset or triggered and
like this is like next level.
So then I snapped it back. I
informed your mother that I'm a 56
year old man, not a 13 year old
boy.
And I said I'm sorry. She said you
made me mad and I interrupted her
and I said no, no, no, no. You made
yourself mad. I didn't make you do
anything.
I think that pissed her off even
more. Anyway, I couldn't send this
to you in a text.
But here I'm sitting in your mom's
basement and I'm at the point where
I'm ready to pack up my fucking car
and I'll go to King Super's fucking
parking lot.
Or actually Walmart. I know where
that is. I don't know Walmart will
kick me out.
I don't know what the fuck to do.
Maybe I should sleep in my car.
Maybe I should go over to Tree in
Bounds and sleep over there.
They're not home. Scotty's here. I
just don't know what the fuck to
do. It just sucks that I had such a
great day.
I was looking forward to coming
home and painting because I went to
the Picasso exhibit today at the
museum and I got really inspired.
And now I just came home and got
fucking attacked.
This is the last thing I need. I've
been really good. I've stayed away
from the news. I've stayed away
from all the things that I know
will trigger me. And the universe
fucking delivered this.
I'll leave it there. Stop crying.
This is big, okay? It's a big file.
It's like six gigs. I'll try to
make it smaller before I send it.